Guide to the Chimera Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Manuscript Submissions, 1943-47; Series III; 0.5; (2 boxes)
  - Submissions to Vol. V, No. 4, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 191)
    Includes: "Requiescat" by Jacques Barzun; translation of Roger Caillois' Order and License: The Ambiguity of the Detective Story by William Jay Smith; "Notes on Primitive Modes of Detection" by Jector Hoppin; "Imperfect Myths" by Jose F. Montesinos.
  - Submissions to Vol. V, No. 4, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 192)
    Includes: "Graham Greene" by Donat O'Donnell; "The Detective Story Mystery" by G. Robert Stange; "A Trinity Of 'Tecs: From There to Where?" by Ruthven Todd; "Who'd Do It?: An Apologia for Mystery Novelists" by Q. Patrick.
  - Unpublished Submissions, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 193)
    Includes: "The Mythic Heritage Of Poetry" by Hermann Broch; "Morning", "The Tree" and "Sky" by P.B.C.; "The Achievement Of Burma" by Maurice Collis; "Sketch of Modern Dutch Literature" by Wolfgang Cordan; "Cock Haycock and Shuffle" by Richard Easton; "A Catholic Cemetery by a Southern Sea," "My Looking Glass," "Eternity" and "Dust to Dust" by Eugenic of Greece.
  - Unpublished Submissions, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 194)
    Includes: review of H. F. Heard's Doopelgangers by Roy Finch; "Eranos: A Scientific Research Centre In Europe Of Today" by Olga Froeba- Kapteyn; "An Oriental Encounter" by Gerald de Gaury; "The Fall And Rise of Baghdad A.D. 1258 -1958; "The Amazons In The Middle East" by Gerald de Gaury; "The Tulip Sultan" by Gerald de Gaury; editorial statement on detective issue (corrected); "The Spiritual Origins of National Socialism" by Erich von Kahler; "The Matelot Has A Bath," [author unknown]; "Europe's Battered Muse" by Leo Lania; "Under The Volcano" by Malcolm Lowry.